

IORDANIS CHATZIEVGENIADIS

UI/UX Designer

Creative-Passionate-Experienced

□ ch.iordanis@gmail.com

20/10 Balfour Place, Edinburgh EH65DW

07599886263

Technical Skills -

Operating Systems: Linux, Mac OSX, Windows, Mikrotik.

Languages and Software: Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, Indesign, HTML(5), CSS(3), SASS, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript, Wordpress, Joomla, Sketch, InVision, Axure, Director, Autocad, Blender, Rhinoceros 3D, Microsoft Office.

Networking: LAN, WLAN, DHCP, VPN (PPTP, L2TP, OpenVPN)

Key Skills

'Creativity and imagination 'Understanding of current trends and styles 'Teamwork/interpersonal skills 'Meet deadlines

'Work under pressure

'Ability to find practical solutions to problems 'IT skills

Personal Interests

I love sports such as rowing, kite surfing, rock climbing and capoeira. I studied flute in a music school for 7 years and I played the bass in a band. My main hobbies are chess, computer networks and fishing. I am also keeping up to date with new technologies.

Portfolio -

Feel free to have a look at my work

Employment History

Dec 2018-Present Product Lead at Lendingcrowd. 23 Manor Place, **Edinburgh EH3 7DX**

Responsibilities:

Identifying design problems and devise elegant solutions.

Developing UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look like.

Working in agile an environment.

Preparing and presenting rough drafts to internal teams and key stakeholders. Communicating design ideas and prototypes to developers. Cooperating with project managers and the QA team to ensure that the final product meets the requirements.

Developing the front end part of the platform using HTML, CSS, Javascript and **JQuery**

Sep 2017- Dec 2018 UI/UX Designer at NN4M. Strathmore Business Centre 8B McDonald Road Edinburgh EH7 4LZ

Responsibilities:

User researching, building user personas, creating user stories /scenario maps, wireframes and Interaction Prototypes for both iOS and Android smart phones and tablets, doing metrics analysis, updating and maintaining the company's website and CMS platform.

Creating mobile webviews by using HTML and CSS as a part of the final application.

Oct 2016-Sep 2017 Junior Web Developer at Trendzer Ltd. 99 Giles St, **Edinburgh EH6 6BZ**

Responsibilities:

Writing code in several programming and scripting languages, such as HTML or JavaScript.

Creating responsive website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS and bootstrap practices.

Testing sites and applications in different browsers and environments.

Creating sample page layouts including text size and colours.

Designing graphics, company logos and manipulating digital photographs.

Jan 2014-Mar 2016 Freelance Graphic Designer

Responsibilities:

Develop graphics for product illustrations, logos and websites.

Meet with clients or the art director to determine the scope of a project and create images that identify a product or convey a message.

Education

Oct 2015-May 2016 MSc in Post-Industrial Design: Design and Artistic Practices for the Production of Everyday Life.

University of Thessaly, Greece.

Feb 2005-Sep 2014 Faculty of Fine Arts And Design Department of Graphic **Arts Technology**

BA (Hons) in Graphic Design.

Technological Educational Institute of Athens.

Jun 2011 THM Technische Hochschule Mittelhessen University of Applied Sciences in Friedberg, Germany

Media Informatics and Computer Graphics course.

Sep 2003-Jun 2004 1st Technical Professional/ Vocational School of Argyroupoli in Athens, Greece

Diploma of Interior Designer.